[
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 1969?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Rod Laver",
      "yellow": "Stan Smith",
      "blue": "Ken Rosewall",
      "green": "John Newcombe"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 1976?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Björn Borg",
      "yellow": "Arthur Ashe",
      "blue": "Jimmy Connors",
      "green": "John McEnroe"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 1980?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Björn Borg",
      "yellow": "Ivan Lendl",
      "blue": "John McEnroe",
      "green": "Jimmy Connors"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 1985?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Boris Becker",
      "yellow": "Ivan Lendl",
      "blue": "Stefan Edberg",
      "green": "John McEnroe"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 1990?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Ivan Lendl",
      "yellow": "Pete Sampras",
      "blue": "Stefan Edberg",
      "green": "Boris Becker"
    },
    "correct": "yellow"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 1995?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Andre Agassi",
      "yellow": "Michael Chang",
      "blue": "Pete Sampras",
      "green": "Boris Becker"
    },
    "correct": "blue"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 2001?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Pete Sampras",
      "yellow": "Patrick Rafter",
      "blue": "Andre Agassi",
      "green": "Lleyton Hewitt"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 2004?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Andy Roddick",
      "yellow": "Marat Safin",
      "blue": "Roger Federer",
      "green": "Lleyton Hewitt"
    },
    "correct": "blue"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 2008?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Roger Federer",
      "yellow": "Andy Murray",
      "blue": "Rafael Nadal",
      "green": "Novak Djokovic"
    },
    "correct": "yellow"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 2012?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Andy Murray",
      "yellow": "Rafael Nadal",
      "blue": "Roger Federer",
      "green": "Novak Djokovic"
    },
    "correct": "blue"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 2016?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Andy Murray",
      "yellow": "Stan Wawrinka",
      "blue": "Novak Djokovic",
      "green": "Roger Federer"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 2019?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Novak Djokovic",
      "yellow": "Andy Murray",
      "blue": "Roger Federer",
      "green": "Rafael Nadal"
    },
    "correct": "red"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won Wimbledon (Men's Singles) in 2023?",
    "answers": {
      "red": "Novak Djokovic",
      "yellow": "Nick Kyrgios",
      "blue": "Carlos Alcaraz",
      "green": "Daniil Medvedev"
    },
    "correct": "blue"
  }
]